(Leonard:)I can't believe you're
married to that idiot.
(Penny:)Would you stop?
We just did it as a goof.
(Leonard:)Well, a goof or not,
you're actually married.
(Leonard:)You need to get
this taken care of.
(Penny:)I will. Why are you
making this such a big deal?
Oh! I have a reason.
(Sheldon:)It could be because
you said yes to marrying Zack,
(Sheldon:)but every time
Leonard's proposed,
(Sheldon:)he's gotten a resounding no.
(Sheldon:)That's just off the top of my head.
(Penny:)So how do I undo this?
(Leonard:)I'm hoping you can
get an annulment,
so it's just like
it never happened.
(Penny:)Great, well, what do I have to do?
(Amy:)It says here
you can get an annulment
(Amy:)if any of the following
conditions are met.
"Were you unable
to consummate the marriage?"
(Sheldon:)Penny? Next.
"Is there any evidence
of fraud, bigamy,
want of understanding?"
(Amy:)Want of understanding?
(Penny:)What does that even mean?
(Amy:)Ding, ding, ding.
We have a winner.
(Bernadette:)Thanks for saving the day.
(Raj:)No problem.
(Raj:)It wouldn't be Thanksgiving
(Raj:)without an Indian
providing the food.